[Music] let's see I
[Música]
have it here to see what
a ver Es que tengo por aquí para ver lo
Claro has a little to do with this let's see
de claro tiene un poco que ver con esto
wait wesco explodes with ibai
a ver espera wesco le explota con ibai
ibai is a rat or rather to such an extent they have
ibai es una rata o sea hasta tal punto
eh To such an extent they have
se han eh Hasta tal punto se han
reserved themselves or rather they have gotten so heated up
reservado o sea se han calentado tanto
until reaching this or rather this was
hasta llegar a esto o sea esto era
arguing about who of the two gets paid
discutiendo de quién de los dos cobra
more one saying I get paid more than IV
más el uno diciendo Yo cobro más que IV
surely and the other saying what a movie you've
seguramente y el otro diciendo vaya peli
put together Javi I made three videos
qued has montado Javi hice tres videos
with the singer koala the real one I uploaded
con el cantante koala el de verdad subí
one to tiktok another to Instagram and another
uno a tiktok otro a Instagram y otro
YouTube and Sorry if I'm heavy what's
YouTube y Perdona si soy pesado qué va
up What's up what's up domi you Here you here you get a kiss a kiss then I'll see them then I'll see them okay But come on I think domi's career is impressive Congratulations all the controversy has been dragging on for a while in part because the way of clicking has been criticized
en parte porque yva criticado la forma
talking about how
de click hablando de que allá se inflan
the visits are inflated there by finger and of course that
las visitas a dedo y claro eso
indirectly is a criticism of the
indirectamente es una crítica a los
creators of that platform Well it's not
creadores de esa plataforma Bueno no es
a criticism of the creators of that
una crítica a los creadores de esa
platform it's that they really  think it is
plataforma es que realmente se piensa se
thought that there are that they are not very real
piensa que hay que que no son muy reales
but well we will see them we will see them it is
pero bueno los iremos viendo los iremos
thought I do not know if it is true or not
viendo se piensa no sé si es verdad o no
to me there are Some numbers of some
a mí hay Algunos números de algunos
creators that seem like [ __ ] crazy to me
creadores que me parecen una [__] locura
What you say Damn but these numbers
Que tú dices [__] pero estos números
Damn but all these users have
[__] pero todos estos usuarios tienen
this platform no longer because of the creator
esta plataforma ya no por el creador
as such but because of the platform eh I mean
como tal sino por la plataforma eh o sea
No it is not because of the creator it is because of the
No no es por el creador es por la
platform it is like so many people have
plataforma es como tanta gente tiene
these people but everything exploded as a result of
esta gente pero todo explotó a raíz de
a question from ibai about whether
una pregunta de ibai sobre si a los
or not the foker have a Bot this is where hco
foker tiene o no Bot es acá donde hco le
explodes Because although the question is
explota Porque si bien la pregunta es
about the foker president of the
sobre a los foker presidente del equipo
Galactico del Caribe team of the King leit it
de galáctico del Caribe de la King leit
is a live attack on his image
es un ataque en directo a su imagen
also because saying that the creators
también porque decir que los creadores
of K content have or do not have a Bot is a
de contenido de K tienen o no Bot es un
disregard for the work of these people
menosprecio al trabajo de estas personas
and their achievements personally wcol has always
y sus logros personalmente wcol siempre
seemed to me to be a person with a
me ha parecido una persona con un ego
very big ego and who says very
muy grande y que dice cosas muy
controversial things however he is a person who commands
polémicas sin embargo es una persona que
respect both himself and his
se hace respetar tanto a él como a su
work and does not remain silent Although
trabajo y no se queda callado Aunque a
the person to criticize is going to be ibai
la persona a criticar vaya a ser ibai A
Let's see what  has said wescol ibai
ver vamos a ver qué ha dicho wescol ibai
is a rat for me ibai too is
es una rata también para mí ibai me está
making me angry brother really dog
dando ya rabia brother de verdad perro
how I have treated him is with respect
yo yo como he tratado es con respeto
as I have always spoken well of him he has not
como he hablado bien siempre de él se la
given it to him I have always treated him but
ha dado pas siempre lo he tratado pero
well you know [ __ ] Cucho how I have
bien ustedes saben huevón Cucho como yo
treated Cucho does Speaking clearly with
he tratado hace Cucho Hablando claro con
respect always [ __ ] always pa I have never
respeto siempre huevón siempre pa nunca
disrespected him and that [ __ ] can't
le faltado el respeto y ese huevón no
see that someone has more viewers
puede ver que alguien tenga más viewers
than him because he uses Bots Ah here aofo
que él porque usa Bots Ah aquí que aofo
uses Bots also how is he going to use bz alofo
usa Bots también cómo va usar bz alofo
What happens is that like that the only one who
Qué pasa es que como así el único que
can have people here is him or what Ah it's that it's
puede tener gente aquí es é o qué Ah es
the real brother one can't
que es la real brother uno no puede
have visits because he has Bots Why do
tener visitas porque tiene Bots Por qué
n't they remove the du by once and for all
no le quitan la du by de una vez
show me days of viewers on Twitch that
muéstrenme dia de viewers en Twitch que
I arrived four days in a row putting in
llegaba yo cuat días seguidos metiendo
100,000 people remember Ah ta ta
100,000 personas acuerdan Ah ta ta
100,000 people When had you
100,000 personas Cuándo usted había
seen that nothing I was more glued to
visto eso nada yo estaba más pegado en
Twitch than the punch when I came
Twitch que la puña cuando me vine para
here brother My last live on Twitch  It
acá brother Mi último directo en Twitch
was 145,000 people so what do I use
fue de 145,000 personas entonces qué uso
votes everywhere dude my likes on
vots en todos lados huevón mis likes en
instagram what 400,000 likes for each
instagram qué 400,000 likes por cada
photo as if I were an old woman in thongs
foto como si fuera una vieja an tangas
daddy how lazy but he threw the phone that
papi qué pereza pero le tiró al ofo que
you pa you have thrown us both you have
usted pa nos ha tirado a los dos nos ha
thrown us both that is
tirado a los dos es que eso es
discrediting the work my brother that
desacreditar el trabajo mi hermano que
you take and a person comes to you that
usted coja y le llegue una persona que
the person has viers and from one that you
la persona tenga viers y de una eso
know what that Not even discrediting
sabes qué eso Ni si quiera desacreditar
the work That is arrogance dude And that
el trabajo Eso es arrogancia huevón Y
is feeling you feel overshadowed feeling
eso es sentisse sentisse opacado
overshadowed gold because what's
sentisse opacado oro porque es que que
wrong with another person having
que tiene de malo que otra persona tenga
viewers then they are forced to
viewers entonces obligado tiene que
have Bots Well if someone reaches a certain
tener Bots Pues si alguien llega a una
amount of viewers they are forced to
cantidad de viewers obligado tiene que
be Bots but if they go and nail 4 million
ser Bots pero si va y clava 4 millones
viewers no no no none of them are Bots Of course
de viewers no no no ninguno es Bot Claro
not daddy you are the best that daddy that that that that is
que no papi usted es el mejor eso papi
being a rat that is being a
eso eso eso eso es ser una rata eso es
rat for me leave it in one
ser una rata pa a mí déjelo en uno
camelar because it is that I am on
camellar pues que es que yo estoy en
another platform I am relaxed  I'm
otra plataforma estoy relajado estoy
calm I mean with respect always has
tranquilo me refiero con respeto siempre
Cucho So what's the problem
ha Cucho Entonces cuál es el problema
well
pues
Ah and then one the problem no I think it's
Ah y después uno el problema no yo creo
not because of that only eh I think it's been
que no es por eso solo eh yo creo que se
stung by a few more things
ha picado por unas cuantas más de cosas
eh Well it's a lack of respect
eh A lo bien es una falta de respeto
brother that Ah is that one uses Bot come
brother que Ah es que uno usa Bot venga
here see come on rehearse go to all the
para acá ver venga ensaye ve a todos los
Argentinians who are already rehearsing come on see
argentinos que ya están ensayando venga
come on see how many Bots there are Do it
a ver venga a ver cuántos Bots hay Haga
yourself do the
usted mismo la haga usted mismo la
test yourself dude do the test yourself on
prueba huevón hagan mismo la prueba a
everyone I you know what would be a good
todos yo tú sabes cuál sería una buena
test direct from webc on Twitch or on
prueba directo de webc en Twitch o en
YouTube maybe to see platforms in which
YouTube quizá a ver plataformas que en
obviously at least it would have to
las que obviamente como mínimo tendría
have the same or a little less
que tener lo mismo o un poco menos a lo
maybe I don't know okay but I understand that there are
mejor no lo sé vale pero entiendo que se
supposed to be more people on YouTube or
supone que hay más gente en YouTube o en
yes no on YouTube and on and on Twitch no
sí no en YouTube y en y en Twitch no
but of course if the Stream on Kick I don't know if
pero claro si el Stream en Kick no sé si
that one let's see whatever sooner or later I
ese a ver lo que sea tarde o temprano yo
think it will be known eh I take turn
creo que se va a saber eh yo cojo prendo
on a channel without warning on Twitch and I have
en un canal sin avisar en Twitch y tengo
and a channel that is neither mine nor is mine
y un canal que ni es mío ni es mío
dude on Stream we  nailed up to
huevón en Stream hemos clavado hasta
12,000 people strep a Twitch channel
12,000 personas strep un canal de Twitch
that isn't even mine without warning on
que ni siquiera es mío sin avisar en
main networks 12,000 people we've
redes principales 12,000 personas hemos
put there My God really really
metido allá Dios mío de verdad de verdad
[ __ ] contempt partner they have rage step they have
[__] menosprecio socio tienen rabia paso
pa I'm going to tell you something that is something that is something
tienen pa yo les voy a decir algo eso es
net of them because
algo eso es algo neto de ellos pues
they were born with that turn [ __ ] they were
ellos nacieron con esa vuelta huevón
born with that arrogance those desire
nacieron con esa arrogancia esas ganas
Cucho to be superior pa that's the
Cucho de ser superiores pa es la
reality rage is that is a thing that
realidad rabia es eso es una cosa que
you say dude but what What damage is it
usted dice parce pero que Qué daño le
doing to you because one here Ah that is why it is
está haciendo pues uno acá Ah por eso es
difficult for them not even mentioning
que les cuesta no menciona ni el nombre
one's name you saw how much trouble it
de uno ustedes vieron cuánto problema
was brother for them to mention
fue brother para que ellos mencionaran
one's name that arrogance they
el nombre de uno esa arrogancia que
have even I had to be such a
tienen hasta yo tuve que ser una persona
big person for them to be forced to
tan grande para que ellos obligados
mention my name because they didn't
tuvieran que mencionar mi nombre porque
even do it Let's see
ni siquiera lo hacían A ver vamos a ver
what gre has said about this anyone well
qué ha dicho gre sobre esto cualquiera
sometimes he lets his tongue go and says
pues a veces se va de la lengua y dice
things he doesn't have and alofoke very
cosas que no tiene y alofoke muy
upset with ibai for supposedly
molestos con ibai por supuestamente
accusing him of using Bots I didn't hit him so hard
acusarle de usar Bots no le di tan duro
because he was sucking me off  so that he
porque él me lo estaba mamando para que
could get Bad Bunny for the
le consiguiera a Bad Bunny para la
evening [ __ ] I regret having
velada [__] me arrepiento de haberle
sucked his [ __ ] How is that son of a
mamado el [__] Cómo es que ese hijo de
[ __ ] going to tell you you use Bots the son of a
[__] te va a decir usas Bots el hijo de
[ __ ] didn't tell me to my face I threw a
[__] no me lo dijo en la cara le tiro un
bucket honey
cubo miel
gal no so it has to be me right now I'm
gal no así que tiene que ser yo ahorita
also going to throw [ __ ] at him until
también le voy a tirar [__] hasta
until and I threw [ __ ] at him so he learns
hasta y le tiré [__] para que aprenda
to
a
respect the crazy
respetar el
guy I'm going son of a [ __ ]
loco voy hij de la gran [__]
come see with a name no me I already had him no it's
pasar voir con nombre no yo yo ya le tié
that s bro you can't go out and talk
no es que s bro no pueden salir a hablar
like that how is that son of a [ __ ] going to
así cómo es que ese hijo de [__] va
say that you have Bots Oh yeah And that Bot
decir que tenés Bots Ah sí Y que Bot
after I already told it tell me to my face
después yo ya lo dije dímelo en la cara
and he didn't tell me No well what is he going to
y no me lo dijo No pues que te lo va a
tell you bro obviously he's not going to tell you
decir bro obviamente no te lo va a decir
but the son of a [ __ ] didn't tell me to my
pero no me lo dijo el hijo de [__] en la
face and you know why I didn't hit him so
cara y sabes por qué Yo no le di tan
hard because I was sucking him off so I could
duro porque me lo estaba mamando a mí
get him bon
para que le consiguiera bon
dude because I was sucking him off so I could
loco porque me la estaba mamando para
get him Bani for the evening
que le consiguiera Bani para la velada
Well we talked and talked in Bot so
Bueno hablamos y hablamos en Bot pues
[ __ ]  very spicy clip no guys
[__] clip muy salseante no chicos
I'm even a little shocked
incluso estoy un poco impactado
a lot yes yes well well well number ahale I'm going to
mucho sí sí bien bien bien número ahale
save it I'm going to save it well
lo vo a guardar lo vo a guardar bueno
ivai let's say that he has played against himself
ivai digamos que él ha jugado en su
one thing that he always does doesn't
contra una cosa que siempre hace a mí no
surprise me I was watching the live
me sorprende yo estuve viendo el directo
I saw the final 4 of the Americas a little bit
yo vi la final 4 de Américas un poquito
in the live of ibai spursito and Mario and
en el directo de ibai spursito y Mario y
suddenly ibai goes and says Hey spursito do
de repente ibai va y dice Oye spursito
you think that alofoke uses Bots and it's
tú crees que alofoke utiliza Bots y es
something that he does a lot he is very
algo que él hace mucho él se le da muy
good at asking questions in which he pretends
bien hacer preguntas en las que pretende
not to say something and that someone else says it
no no decir algo y que lo diga otra
for him so of course spursito
persona por él entonces claro spursito
told him well sincerely I think
le dijo bueno pues yo sinceramente creo
not And you ivai what do you think But ivai
que no Y tú ivai qué crees Pero eso ivai
does that a lot He sometimes with the people
lo hace mucho Él a veces con la gente de
around him he throws questions that he himself
su alrededor tira preguntas que él mismo
doesn't want to say so that someone else answers them
no quiere decir para que lo responda
and he leaves like that
otro y él se vaya
man How badly they all fall eh how badly
así tío Qué mal se caen todos eh qué mal
gref falls with ibai I mean gref and ibai they ca
se cae gref con ibai o sea gref e ibai
n't see each other man do you remember when I
no se pueden ver tío os acordáis cuando
told you to gref eh well
os lo dije a gref Eh bueno a gref no lo
a few can't see gref and then
pueden ver unos cuantos y luego
publicly you see it like they talk
públicamente lo veis como que se hablan
eh with him and they participate and gref invites them
eh con él y participan y gref los invita
to the elan and they invite them to his
a los elan y ellos los invitan a su
series and to his events I mean they do that
serie y a sus eventos o sea hacen eso
dude but really Then
tío pero en verdad Luego me vienen
some people come to me and tell me about gref's gossip
algunos y me cuentan an salseos de gref
Okay and gref can't see
Vale y y gref tampoco los puede ver a
them either I mean I get the feeling that
ellos o sea a mí me da la sensación que
greev just can't stand him but it's also
greev ahí va no lo soporta pero es que
noticeable eh and b hit out at
aparte ya se notó eh y b le tiró fuerte
greev eh he did something that for me was
a greev eh hizo una cosa que para mí fue
very low which was bringing up the thing about the
muy baja que fue lo de sacarle lo de los
Andorra days Why the [ __ ] are you attacking her
días de andorra Por qué [__] la atacas
with that to her [ __ ] face and then gref
con eso por la [__] cara y luego gref se
came back at her with the thing that I go and pay
la devolvió con el tema de que I va y
taxes as a society they can't see each other they can't
tributa como sociedad no se pueden ver
see each other dude I don't understand
no se pueden ver tío yo no entiendo las
collaborations like that between people you
colaboraciones así entre gente con la
don't get along with and such dude I mean I
que no te llevas y tal tío o sea
understand that there are places where you have to
entiendo que hay sitios donde tienes que
coincide for example imagine a
coincidir por ejemplo imagínate un
big event and such they invite you but since
evento grande y tal te invitan pero ya
it's your [ __ ] your [ __ ] event invite
que sea tu [__] tu [__] evento invitar a
a guy to  that you can't stand or I don't know the
un pavo al que no soportas o no sé la
truth I try to put myself in the place no I
verdad intento ponerme en el lugar no O
mean I put myself and I say Well I would go to
sea yo me pongo y digo Bueno yo iría a
an event of a guy that I can't stand and
un evento de un pavo que no soporto y en
actually yes no if you like the event yes
realidad sí no si te gusta el evento sí
no if you like the event yes no no but
no si te gusta el evento sí no no pero
of course one thing is that you go to an
claro una cosa es que tú vayas a un
event because I think that I would do that
evento porque creo que eso sí lo haría
but for example what I wouldn't do would be
pero por ejemplo lo que no haría sería
a buddy a collaboration maybe
un compadre una colaboración a lo mejor
not a Oh come on I'll paint you The
no un Ay venga te te pinto La Casita del
Minecraft House come on then you paint it for
Minecraft venga pues tú me la pintas a
me maybe it wouldn't be there the
mí a lo mejor por ahí no estaría el la
line not because of the brands yes no just because of
línea no por las marcas sí no solo por
the brands let's see for example for me the
las marcas a ver yo por ejemplo a mí los
hland for example I would like to go the
hland por ejemplo me gustaría ir la
evening maybe it doesn't call me that much the
velada a lo mejor no me llama tanto la
hland calls me bad the hland I would go
los hland me llama mal los hland se iría
dude because it's like a compilation not
tío porque es como una recopilación no
of it's like a compilation of all the of
de es como una recopilación de todos los
all the streamers no of all the
de todos los streamers no de todos los
streamers of the year and all the moments
streamers del año y todos los momentos
of the year I don't know I like it more maybe the
del año no sé me Mola más a lo mejor la
truth is it's more sporty and for me you
verdada es más deportivo y a mí ya
know that sport is not no  it's a lot of
sabéis que el deporte no es no es mucho
my thing no but of course I wouldn't go like to
lo mío no pero claro no iría como para
be with gref mmm you [ __ ] go to gref
estar con gref mmm tú pelote hase a gref
when you met him at the calamar
cuando te lo encontraste en el calamar
well the fact is that I didn't meet him
bueno es que de hecho no me lo encontré
he came to [ __ ] I armed your dad Javi
vino él a pelote arme a tu papá Javi
Olivera he came Javi Olivera I don't know what I don't know
Olivera vino él Javi Olivera no sé qué
how much don't make me a video and I
no sé cuánto no me hagas un vídeo y yo
went along with it what am I going to do
le seguí el rollo que voy a hacer
spit on him but yes yes I understand that it's
escupirle pero sí sí entiendo que es
work Yes let's see I understand that it's work
trabajo Sí a ver entiendo que es trabajo
but there are other things that I don't understand
pero hay otras cosas que no las entiendo
there of course the thing is that I know
hay claro es que el tema es que yo sé
other things that you don't things let's see
otras cosas que ustedes no cosas a ver
okay look I'm going to set the limit here
vale mira os voy a poner el límite aquí
okay And you're going to understand okay I buy you
vale Y lo Vais a entender vale Te compro
that I would go because I would do it okay I
que iría porque yo lo haría vale Yo me
try to put myself in the shoes okay of the one I'm
intento poner en los zapatos vale del
going to criticize And of what I'm going to
que voy a criticar Y de lo que voy a
criticize So I put myself and I say
criticar Entonces yo me pongo y digo
damn what a lie I don't know I know how much but I
[__] qué falsedad no sé sé cuánto pero
say eh I would do it too you might be
digo eh yo también lo haría te puede
interested Up to a certain limit eh like
interesar Hasta cierto límite eh o sea
for example I rejected the evening for the
por ejemplo la velada la rechacé por los
reasons that you already know okay But okay Eh
motivos que ya sabéis vale Pero bueno Eh
yes you might be interested  you take some
sí te puede interesar te hac unas
pictures in the photocall you pose no And you
fotitos en el fotocol posas no Y te
get elegant with your girlfriend and you
pones elegante con la parienta y te
get Cool no eh And also because you
pones Guay no eh Y además porque te
like the experience okay Yes yes but up to
guste la experiencia vale Sí sí pero
certain limits no but now I'll
hasta ciertos límites no pero ahora te
give you another example And if there were
pongo otro ejemplo Y si hubieran temas
personal issues When I say personal issues it
personales Cuando digo temas personales
means that something has happened between you since it
es que haya pasado algo entre ustedes ya
goes further Imagine that
que vaya más allá Imagínate que ha
something serious has happened and a streamer has said
pasado algo grave y un streamer ha dicho
something super serious about your sister or your
algo super grave de tu hermana o de tu
girlfriend or your mother I know something
novia o de tu madre yo que sé algo
personal serious you understand and that
personal grave me entiendes y que por
behind you both go putting each other
detrás vayáis los dos mutuamente
down I don't know the truth of course there are
poniendo verde no sé la verdad claro es
serious things I put myself in another place of
que hay cosas graves yo me pongo en otra
course when I'm saying it No it's not to
claro cuando lo estoy diciendo No no es
put myself in the shoes of Oh how
por ponerme en los sapatos de Ay qué
false this one goes to the other's event no me
falso este va al evento del otro no yo
for example about the evening is what I'm
por ejemplo lo de la velada es lo que te
telling you, I mean there was an important issue
digo o sea había tema importante de por
involved they invite me to the candle this
medio a mí me invitan a la vela de este
year and the same thing I take and I go eh I mean yes I
año y lo mismo cojo y me voy eh o sea yí
go yes why not I mean in fact
voy sí por qué no O sea de hecho está
Fran is there probably this year eh I wouldn't be
por allí Fran seguramente este año eh No
surprised in fact if he went to
me extrañaría de hecho que fuera a
Madrid to  go to Fran those days if he stays
Madrid a ve a Fran esos días si se queda
around or whatever eh What's
por aquí o lo que sea eh Qué hay en
against the evening this year you
contra de la velada este año me
know what I mean But let's see what the
entiendes Pero a ver que es que la
evening is, man, it's not something that I have You
velada tío no es una cosa que me hve a
know what it's a sport, man It's that for me that
mí Sabes qu es deporte tío Es que a mí
maybe for the red carpet Yeah
eso a lo mejor para la alfombra roas Sí
but then swallowing the whole evening I don't
pero luego tragarme la velada entera no
feel like it but
me apetece pero
Eh there are certain personal things between
Eh hay ciertas cosas personales entre
youtubers that don't make sense
youtubers que no que no tienen sentido
then you don't V no longer see them at an
luego ya no V ya no vértelos en un
event because you can even go to an
evento porque tú puedes incluso ir a un
event this big where they're all
evento así de grande donde estén todos
okay, it's seeing them play live
vale ya es vértelo jugar en directos
together with each other I don't want to
juntos uno con el otro Es que no quiero
give more details But there is one fact that is the
dar más datos Pero hay un dato que es la
[ __ ] there is one fact that is the [ __ ] [ __ ]
[__] hay un dato que es la [__] [__]
you guys see it as normal that Ari presents The
ustedes veis normal que Ari presente Los
eslan I don't know maybe you guys see it
eslan No sé a lo mejor ustedes lo veis
differently than me but it's that and and I don't know on the
diferente a mí pero es que y y no sé por
part of the three is worse
parte de cuál de los tres es peor
So what happens is that this has sat
Entonces qué pasa que esto le ha sentado
very badly with loke and westcol and I was there at that
muy mal a loke y westcol e yo estuve ese
moment I know of the moment when they talk
momento se de el momento de que hablan
because they said it about alofoke and then he
porque lo lo dijeron de alofoke y luego
came in  alofoke on the call and they were
entró alofoke en la llamada y estaban
all like that Then Well for me it doesn't
todos así Enton Bueno para mí a gren no
leave gren bad in any way eh I
lo deja mal en ninguno de los sentido eh
mean gre that gre that is good Eh if it is that it is
o sea gre que gre que es bueno Eh si es
always the same guys we spend
que es lo de siempre chicos pasamos
many hours live and here even the
muchas horas en directo y aquí hasta el
smartest the dumbest and anyone well
más listo el más tonto y cualquiera pues
sometimes he talks and says things he should
a veces se va de la lengua y dice cosas
n't say it has happened to
que no tiene que decir nos ha pasado a
all of us and the discount will happen to us the discount
todos y nos pasará la rebaja la rebaja
but man I mean you made it green albay
pero tío O sea la has puesto verde albay
[ __ ] now discount now discount eh but you
cabrón ahora rebaja ahora rebaja eh pero
made it green you made it green
la has puesto verde la has puesto verde
[ __ ] Ah come on it's okay gref say it say it
cabrón Ah va no pasa nada gref dilo dilo
gref [ __ ] don't [ __ ] yourself I don't know that's
gref cabrón no te cagues no sé por ahí
where I see Maybe a little bit of the
es donde yo veo A lo mejor un poco el
limit and how far it can be falsified
límite y de hasta dónde se puede falsear
or not obviously it is work is what I'm
o no evidentemente es trabajo es lo que
telling you I mean I would go to places
te digo o sea yo sí asistiría a sitios
where I can't see others or
donde yo no me pueda ver con otros o
where I coincide with others anyway Look, I'll
donde coincid con otros sea Es que mira
give you the example This is
te pongo el ejemplo Es que esto es
work okay I mean look at how far it is
trabajo vale o sea fijaros hasta dónde
work I'll give you an example Okay
es trabajo que te pongo un ejemplo Vale
and you'll understand I think  I don't know that you
y lo Vais a entender yo creo a no sé que
're idiots, okay, eh, imagine if they
seáis imbéciles vale eh si tú imagínate
call me to collaborate on one
A mí que me llaman para colaborar a un
of these gossip shows, not now
programa de estos del cotilleo No ahora
that I'm into the whole telesalseo thing and all this
que estoy con lo de telesalseo y todo el
stuff about reality shows and
rollo este de los reality y las cosas de
tele5 stuff, no, they're probably going to take me
tele5 No a mí me van a llevar
with someone else who'll
seguramente con otro con el que me lleve
kill me so that on the set we can
a matar para que allí en el plató
debate and discuss and all that stuff, they're
debatamos y discutamos y todo el rollo
not going to take all the
no van a llevar a todos los
collaborators who think the same, you know
colaboradores que piensen igual sabes
that, it's logical, okay, but there are other
eso Es lógico vale pero yo hay otras
things that I don't see as logical, I don't know,
cosas ya que no las veo lógicas no sé
but I'm telling you. I mean, maybe
pero yo te digo O sea a lo mejor ya las
I don't know about things from within each person's life, I don't know. [
cosas yo de dentro de la vida de cada
Music]
[Música]
Oh
sé Oh